farsinet.com 2010-06-26

# FarsiNet Privacy Statement

FarsiNet takes seriously the issue of safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following to understand our views and practices regarding this matter, and how they pertain to you as you make full use of our many offerings. This statement discloses the privacy practices for the entire Web site. 

_**FarsiNet does not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any personal information collected at our site, including membership forms or email lists.**_

We are very conscious of your right to privacy regarding the information you supply to FarsiNet. At FarsiNet, our policy is to use the information you supplied to us only to better serve you. **We are not going to sell your information to people who want to send you junk mail.** We have adopted a comprehensive set of security measures to ensure that your personal, business and financial information is protected at all times. Specifically, any financial data supplied by you will be kept completely confidential in an electronic, encrypted state. In addition, any confidential data coming to us or going to our provider partners travels across the internet in an encrypted form.

If you choose to purchase business services through FarsiNet and our provider partners, we may need to send those providers limited information from your profile, such as your name and address. We will send only the information needed to complete your transaction. Just as importantly, we are committed to working only with transaction partners who agree to abide by the same privacy rules that we have adopted for FarsiNet.

|  **_We do not use cookies on this site._**  
---  
  
Profile information will be used to create personalized content and services from our FarsiNet site. In addition, FarsiNet and its licensees may use aggregated information from profiles to provide our partners with information that will help them, and thereby us, to serve you better. 

FarsiNet reserves the right to change it's policy at any time, but will notify you of any changes. Should a privacy dispute arise, FarsiNet will be held harmless and not liable for any loses that may have been incurred. If you want additional information or clarification, please email us at, [customer service](mailto:customerservice@farsinet.com?subject=Privacy%20Inquiry), with your specific questions. We will be more than happy to answer them. 

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through email, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Furthermore, while we strive to protect your personal information, FarsiNet cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, nd you do so at your own risk. In addition, FarsiNet partners and third party Internet sites and services accessible hrough FarsiNet or parties whom we inform you are collecting data in connection with sweepstakes, promotions, etc., have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of us. FarsiNet has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions. The point? You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.  FarsiNet is a member of [The Online Privacy Alliance](http://www.privacyalliance.org/)  
---
